Speaker 1: you
Speaker 1: the
Speaker 1: Pain stays mainly in...
Speaker 1: in the
Speaker 2: What was that?
Speaker 1: The rain in Spain stays mainly
Speaker 1: in the place
Speaker 2: Again?
Speaker 1: The rain in Spain stays mainly in the past.
Speaker 2: I think she's gone.
Speaker 2: I think she's got it.
Speaker 1: The
Speaker 3: rain and
Speaker 1: Mainly in the play
Speaker 2: Bye, George.
Speaker 2: By George, he's got it.
Speaker 2: Now once again, where does it race?
Speaker 3: On the plane, on the plane
Speaker 2: And where's that soggy plane?
Speaker 3: In Spain, in Spain
Speaker 2: is
Speaker 3: is
Speaker 3: you
Speaker 2: Bravo!
Speaker 3: In the face
Speaker 2: In Hartford, Hereford and Hampshire.
Speaker 3: Hurricanes hardly happen.
Speaker 3: How kind of you to let
Speaker 2: Let me come.
Speaker 2: Where does it rest?
Speaker 3: On the plane, on the plane
Speaker 2: And where's that blaster?
Speaker 3: In Spain, in Spain
Speaker 4: Oh
Speaker 4: Yeah.
Speaker 4: Hey!
Speaker 4: Oh! Hey!
Speaker 4: Oh!
Speaker 4: Oh, no!